// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
  {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Which 3 levels in OSI Model are usually implemented in the software within the operating system? ",
    answer: "Application, Presentation, Session",
    options: [
      "Application, Presentation, Session ",
      "Data Link, Transport, Application",
      "Transport, Session, Presentation",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "Which of these protocols reside in Layer 3 - Network in the OSI Model?",
    answer: "IP and IPSec",
    options: [
      "TCP and IPSec",
      "IP and TCP",
      "IP and IPSec",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 3,
    question: "Shortening an IPv6 address means:",
    answer: "Removing a group of only 0's",
    options: [
      "Converting 8 groups of 4 hexadecimal numbers into a valid IPv4 address ",
      "Removing unused groups of hexadecimal numbers",
      "Removing a group of only 0's",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "What is IDOR?",
    answer: "Insecure Direct Object Reference",
    options: [
      "Invalid Data or Reference ",
      "Insecure Direct Object Reference",
      "Insecure Door or Room",
      "None of the above"
    ]
  },
  {
  numb: 5,
  question: "What is best practice in defending against SQL injection?",
  answer: "Sanitizing users input in a web application",
  options: [
    "Sanitizing users input in a web application  ",
    "Programmers will not make web applications that allow user input",
    "Blocking specific ports that SQL injections are usually attacked via",
    "None of the above"
  ]
},
{
numb: 6,
question: "What is CSP - Content Security Policy?",
answer: "A strict way of controlling where javascript is allowed to be executed from",
options: [
  "TLS encryption between server and client",
  "A strict way of controlling where javascript is allowed to be executed from ",
  "A strict way of sanitizing user input on a website",
  "None of the above"
]
},
{
numb: 7,
question: "Which order of security protocols is correct, going from least to most secure?",
answer: "WEP, WPA, WPA2, WPA3 ",
options: [
  "WPA, WPA2, WPA3, WEP  ",
  "WPA, WEP, WPA2, WPA3",
  "WEP, WPA, WPA2, WPA3",
  "None of the above"
]
},
{
numb: 8,
question: "Classifications of incidents should generally be according to?",
answer: "Category, sensitivity, criticality, SLA, contact channel",
options: [
  "Category, sensitivity, criticality, SLA, contact channel   ",
  "Category, sensitivity, criticality",
  "Category, sensitivity, criticality, SLA",
  "None of the above"
]
},
{
numb: 9,
question: "The 6 stages of PICERL are:",
answer: "Preparation, Identification, Containment, Eradication, Recovery, Lessons Learned ",
options: [
  "Preparation, Identification, Containment, Eradication, Recovery, Payment  ",
  "Preparation, Identification, Containment, Eradication, Recovery, Vacation",
  "Preparation, Identification, Containment, Eradication, Recovery, Lessons Learned ",
  "None of the above"
]
},
{
numb: 10,
question: "In which phase of PICERL is blocking attackers usually done?",
answer: "Containment",
options: [
  "Containment",
  "Preparation",
  "Identification",
  "Eradication"
]
}
    
];